nextworth.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | NextWorth

**Effective Date: March 23, 2015

NextWorth Solutions, Inc. protects your privacy. We strive to keep your personal information confidential.

**  
Your privacy is our priority and we understand that you entrust us with the security of your information.

This Privacy Policy outlines the collection of, type of and use and disclosure of Personal Information that is collected by NextWorth Solutions, Inc. (NextWorth, we, us, our) from consumers and our Client on our Web site www.nextworth.com and through the NextWorth Platform and how we use and protect it. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged NextWorth Solutions, Inc.

NextWorth Solutions, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements (http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) and TRUSTed Cloud Program Requirements (http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/TRUSTed-cloud/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe certification covers only our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website www.nextworth.com and our service NextWorth platform and does not cover information that may be collected through printed promotional materials, comment cards, sweepstakes entry forms, or other mail in offers or telephone calls. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at customerservice@nextworth.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [ TRUSTe. ](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

NextWorth Solutions, Inc. complies with the U.S. E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. NextWorth Solutions, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view NextWorth Solutions, Inc.s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

This Policy applies to NextWorths Web site, the NextWorth Platform, and to its collection of data through printed promotional materials such as customer comment cards, sweepstakes entry forms, or other mail-in offers and telephone calls to NextWorth. By providing NextWorth with Personal Information, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted here. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not provide any Personal Information. As used in this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means personally identifiable information such as name, street address, telephone number, drivers license, military ID, federal state or local govt. ID, passport and email address.

**Information We Collect on Our Website**  
In order to use our Web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration we ask for contact information (such as name, address, and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

If you wish to sell a product to us you must provide contact information (such as name, shipping address, email address and phone number) and financial information such as the email address for your paypal account, or your mailing address in order to receive a check in the mail. We use this information so that we may pay you for your products and so that we are able to ensure your payment is sent to the correct person.   
Upon filling out Customer Information in the NextWorth platform, to verify that the age is at least 18 years old by providing government issued ID, such as drivers license, military ID, federal state or local govt. ID, and passport.  
When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. When you supply us with your Personal Information we will use it for the purpose for which it was collected and may use it to send you periodic communications, newsletters, or promotional offers. If you no longer wish to receive newsletters or promotional offers from us, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication, updating your preference within your account on our Web site, or by emailing us at customerservice@nextworth.com. 

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your email address and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. 

**Social Media (Features) and Widgets**  
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like or Share button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Public Forums**  
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at customerservice@nextworth.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that collects personal information.  
This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**Disclosure of Your Information**  
At times we may retain third parties to analyze data we collect, including Personal Information, solely to help us improve our products and our Web site. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. In addition, if you order a product or service from us, we may provide Personal Information to suppliers and other third parties to enable delivery of such product or service, we may also share your information with a credit card processing company who will process your payments on our behalf. These third parties are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any other way and only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

NextWorth does not sell and share your Personal Information to third parties other than as disclosed in this privacy policy. Please note that we will release your Personal Information to any other third party with your prior consent to do so, or if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. 

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

**Tracking Technologies**  
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by NextWorth Solutions Inc. and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

**Log file**  
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. 

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

**Behavioral Advertising**  
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out at http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/ (or if located in the European Union http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Local Storage Objects (Flash/HTML5)**  
We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information.

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html 

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We take reasonable precautions to keep your Personal Information secure. All personal information is subject to restricted access to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at customerservice@nextworth.com.

**Information Related to Data Collected for our Clients**  
We collect information for our clients, and have no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly. If you are a Client and would like to update your account please contact us at customerservice@nextworth.com.

NextWorth may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients.

NextWorth has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the NextWorths Client (the data controller). If the Client requests NextWorth to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days. 

NextWorth will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. NextWorth will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, delete inaccuracies, amend, or deactivate it by making the change within the my account section of the site or by emailing us at customerservice@nextworth.com. We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at the email address listed above. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you or our Client by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Please write to us at CustomerService@NextWorth.com or at NextWorth Solutions, Inc. 900 Technology Park Drive, Suite 200, Billerica, MA 01821, or call us at 888-969-4763 if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy.
